no, no,
no,
no, no, no,
no.
See you
next
time.
Did you really beat that thing, mister?
Yes, with one punch.
Wow, that's insane.
Not too bad for your first
time skinning an animal.
Well, you're a great teacher.
Do you think it might be worth
anything if I brought it to a big town?
Probably, but I'm not sure.
I've never seen a beast
like this one before.
Huh, that's...
Oh, do you recognize it, Chief?
That's the guardian deity of this forest.
Guardian deity?
So is it bad that I killed it?
Oh, no need to worry about that.
It's not like it's one of ours.
Please don't think anything of it.
I doubt it's as simple as that.
Hey, mister, where's the goddess at?
Oh, still fast asleep.
Though it is about time to wake up.
You up, Tachibana?
Oh, hey, good morning.
I swear, my hair is so annoying
it's taking forever to dry.
Sorry.
I promise I'll be more careful next time.
Appreciate it.
It's bad enough the first naked female
body I've seen happen to be yours.
Not too thrilled about that.
I can't believe I'm
your first naked woman.
It's as sad as it is weird.
Might as well get used
to seeing it since we'll
be sharing a bathroom for
however long we're here.
You could be careful so I don't have to.
This sucks.
I was actually kind of
looking forward to, you know,
getting some one-on-one bath time
with this body But I saw just how much
freaking younger it is than my actual age
and I kind of look like my little sister.
So yeah, it's
Well, it can't be all that bad
What is it?
Yunguji, please don't tell me you've
got a thing for child-like blondes.
I will hit you.
Truthfully,
your appearance is
terrifying because of how it
warps the preferences of
anyone who looks at you.
It changes what you're into?
As best I can tell,
there's some kind of magic embedded in
your appearance that supersedes your looks.
Knowing that it can change my thinking
against my will is terrifying.
You need to change back, and soon.
Yeah, I don't know.
I gotta admit, I'm starting to have fun.
I mean, I could never get
under your skin before,
and now it's like it's almost too easy.
Then there's the fact I have the
whole village fawning all over me.
Yep, the attention is doing
wonders for my ego, and...
And you can't wait to go back
to being a man again, right?
Yes, yes, yes, as soon as possible!
Well, alrighty then. It's settled.
I'll help you in any way I can.
And you said that I was terrifying.
So, what's the plan?
I've been asking around,
but it seems like no one has even heard of
this demon lord we're supposed to defeat.
They did mention a big town up ahead.
So we should go there next and see
if there's anything we can learn.
And since we have plenty of travel
funds, we should plan on leaving soon.
Gotcha!
Is it just me, or is my hair
fluffier and shinier than yesterday?
Why is drying women's hair yet another
thing you're freakishly good at?
I passed by a salon.
So you saw it done once and mastered it?
Oh, yeah.
What happened with that fire yesterday?
Seems it rained and that took care of it.
Well, that's good at least.
Please, if you would just calm down.
You expect me to be calm about this?
I came here to settle this peacefully.
But now I see that's impossible.
You weren't satisfied with
just burning down our forest.
You had to make a mockery of
our guardian deity as well.
Choose humans.
Either bring me the criminals responsible
or I will tear this village apart myself!
You know, seeing people angry
like that makes me uncomfortable.
It's hard to watch.
Like when I'd see the newbies at the office
getting yelled at for whatever reason.
It always felt like I was
getting yelled at, too.
Well, I understand what you mean.
In this particular instance, we are
definitely the people that woman's angry with.
You really think so?
So, in conclusion,
we did not in fact burn
down your forest and our
killing of your guardian
deity was in self-defense,
thus making us innocent of all charges.
We're supposed to be apologizing.
Why are you being so aggressive?
The arrogance of you
humans knows no bounds.
I assume you're the ones responsible?
Yes, however, we wish
to negotiate with you.
The guardian deity was the
protector of our sacred forest.
If it attacked, then you were
trespassing on its hallowed grounds.
There's nothing to negotiate.
Well, if it hadn't attacked us,
I wouldn't have had to kill it.
Quit digging us into a
bigger hole, hole digger!
I'm sorry.
My friend here's not
really a people person.
Now apologize to the nice elf.
Hard pass.
Please stop trying to get us killed.
It's hard to believe that we're
arguing with a real elf, though.
Intimidating Scowl aside,
she's really pretty, too.
Hmm.
The small one's cute.
For a human, at least.
That translucent skin.
Those blue eyes.
golden hair and a
well-proportioned face and I
can see some effort in
her appearance however it
pales in comparison to the
magnificence of my beauty
what the heck is going on
she's doing it again if
she could just keep her
clothes on she'd be halfway
normal I'm sure that
you're wondering how such
an exquisite form could
even exist I'll tell you
it's because we elves are
followers of the goddess of
love and beauty she is
generous alluring and
splendid and we are her
people our long ears are clear
proof of our connection
to her if that's true you
must be just as bad as
she is and those ears are
nothing like the one she's
rocking silent you two
admit your crimes and beg
for mercy press your heads
to the ground and sing
praises of my wondrous form
So we just gotta kneel
down and you'll forgive us?
You looks really! Chibana.
There's no need to humiliate ourselves
for an exhibitionist like her.
How dare you!
I think we can both agree there
was a better way to phrase that.
I won't apologize for
speaking the truth regardless.
I'm amazed at how cavalier you
are about being half-naked.
Weren't you even listening?
Of course I was.
Praise your form, you say?
I have no interest in
women in the first place.
And now that I'm accustomed to Tatyabana's
new look, you have nothing I desire.
We're finished here.
Oh man, way to see the
quiet part out loud, buddy.
And?
What's weird about speaking the truth?
What's this?
Once a man sees my luxurious body,
he should be compelled to bring me
gifts and bend to my every whim!
Even the men of this village pay
tribute simply to one my favor, and yes!
Don't they do that because
you're scary when you're upset?
Shh!
All right, let's put it
to a vote then, shall we?
Popularity and beauty go hand in hand!
Dear sweet villagers,
this girl or myself, assemble before
the one you think is most beautiful!
Now I just feel sorry for her.
If it's any consolation, elf lady,
I think you're prettier than me!
Plus, you really shouldn't
take stuff like this seriously.
I know I'm not!
Tachibana, you're rubbing
salt in the wound.
I Suggest you see this as
a learning opportunity.
Maybe rethink your adherence
to your precious deity.
Who knows it might help with
that personality of yours
Don't casually suggest
she abandoned her faith
I see so that's what you are your acolytes
of some heretical religion aren't you?
I bet you brainwash the villagers.
How else could they
have chosen you over me?
It all makes sense now.
Defiling our sacred land, slaughtering
our guardian deity, making a fool of me.
You're trying to undermine
the majesty of our goddess.
I suspected you were someone who couldn't
admit they lost, but this is absurd.
Silence your lying tongue, you heretic!
O goddess, in your exalted
seat, master of the long ears,
I, your humble servant, here and
now, offer my beauty in your honor.
I beseech thee.
Cleanse away this filth before me!
Lucky! Magic!
Don't get too excited.
By eliminating you,
I will restore the proper balance of
this place with me as the most beautiful.
Die for my sake!
You're going to kill us
over something that petty?
She doesn't care who else she might hurt.
We need to get her to the forest.
why'd you you need to be mindful
of physical contact holding hands
should be out of the question sorry
for not thinking what we're being
attacked your cowardice only serves to
delay the inevitable your slanderous
affront to our goddesses a crime
beyond measure death is your penance
I was overzealous and
allowed them to escape.
Satayna. Ultina.
Yes, my lady.
We'll begin searching at once.
Did you really have to treat
me like that back there?
If I hadn't, then you
probably would have died.
Died?
Don't worry.
I'll always protect you, even
if it kills me in the end.
You're such a jerk.
Don't even joke about something like that!
We're in this together to
the bitter end, Jinguuji.
Live or die! You got that?
Yeah, I think I do.
And believe me, I have
no intention of dying.
You know I never give up without a fight.
So what's your plan
for the scary elf lady?
A rock.
My lady! What happened? Are you hurt?
Oh no, your hair!
A very symbol of your elvenhood!
Impossible!
No!
This can't be!
Don't worry, my lady, it's not that bad!
Did you forget you're fighting a woman?
You could have shown a little restraint!
I'll show no restraint to
those who would do you harm.
However, I did not expect a simple stone
to be capable of something like this.
One teensy little breeze and that
would have been her head for sure.
At any rate, now's probably not the
best time to try and talk things out.
We should leave before she recovers
and tries to kill us again.
Those cretins!
They even took our guardian
deity's pelt with them!
Having been so soundly
defeated by those wretches,
I can no longer return to our settlement.
So I will pursue the heretics.
Is that wise?
I will not let them get away with this.
I will humiliate them as they did our
goddess and take back what they've stolen.
And they will suffer the full,
unyielding weight of my wrath
for what they did to my hair!
She may talk a big game, but in the end
she's more petty than she is devout.
She always gets like
this when she's angry.
All that just to take it off again.
Ridiculous.
You've never played a
video game and you've never
read a manga either is
that weird i mean yeah
it Kind of is but that's
an easy fix let's just
play this game together
obviously we should name
the main character hinata
after me we can give
the heroine your name
since it sounds like a
girl's name anyway yours
sounds like a girl's name
too you know how ironic
that we ended up in the
I'm tired!
There's only so much walking
a modern name can take!
This is just stupid!
We don't have much choice.
We're a three-day walk from the town.
No way! Not happening! All right, then.
After your tantrum, we can set
up camp here for the night.
There's nothing like a nice hot bath.
Whoa, is that a full-course meal?
Once the meat is done, it will be.
How did you manage to find all this stuff?
The village huntsmen helped.
I asked some of them to teach me
what was forageable in the area.
So you gathered all these ingredients
and cooked them while I was in the bath?
We had a long day.
Thus, I figured you'd be hungry.
Except now I feel bad. Hang on.
I know exactly what to contribute.
It's party time now!
Let's make the most of it!
We can take these outside and
drink them under the stars!
Cheers to us!
Ah, man, that's good.
Wipe your mustache.
This looks absolutely delicious.
Um, it's good.
It's got a pretty distinct flavor.
You know, in fact, it
reminds me of game meat.
What was it you said this was again?
I'm sorry.
You fed me the Guardian deity, didn't you?
I'd already drained its blood, and
I didn't want it to go to waste.
That's not the issue here!
I'm sorry I wasn't fully honest with you.
I wanted to give you a warm meal
to help you recover your energy.
And you needed the protein
to get back to full strength.
He did all this because
I said I was tired.
Well, all things aside, this
is actually pretty tasty.
Plus, the beer is cold
and the air is crisp.
No complaints here!
Yes, it's a nice night.
I can't wait to taste all the different
kinds of booze this world has.
You're acting like we're
on vacation or something.
And you're acting like
we're back at the office.
It's been all work and no play with you.
Now relax, or you'll stress
yourself bald. Bless you.
We have earned a break.
We've been so busy with work and life.
When's the last time we took it easy?
We're in a different world
with good food and free time.
No one's watching, so why
not kick back for once?
I hadn't thought of that.
Very well.
It has been quite a while since
I allowed myself to take a break.
And you want to know what the best
part of being in a different world is?
We do what we want.
Stop. What are you doing?
Someone told me if I get too hot
I should take off my clothes.
And I see that you're drunk.
I can't be drunk.
I just had a sip of beer.
That is true, but of course you've
never imbibed with your new body.
you've lost your tolerance.
That explains why everything's suddenly
up and decided to start getting wobbly.
It's the stupid tiny body
being stupid and tiny.
Quit babbling.
I think you've had enough tonight.
You can finish it tomorrow. Okay?
You idiot.
You're forgetting our world's
rules don't apply here.
So, I'll do what I want to!
I have liberation!
Don't run off naked!
And still the same troublesome drunk.
But wandering off semi-nude
is definitely a new feature.
Could it be that it was more than
just the body that was changed?
No.
It's probably an effect
of some kind of skill.
Okay...
It seems this window pops up when I'm
thinking about the skills and their effects.
But the effect of this so-called
blessing is utterly useless.
Jenga J!
No! Tachibana!
Are you all right?
What happened?
I'm not sure how or why, but
I think I'm stuck. Wait there.
I'll get you down.
Could you hurry?
All my blood is starting
to rust in my head
and the springy rope
stuff is super annoying.
No! Can't look!
What's the matter?
Why can't I see anything?
You've been caught by some
strange sort of plant.
Jinguuji, where are you?
What's going on?
This is bad.
There's too much skin exposed.
I don't want to look.
Are you still there?
Am I...
both by myself?
Would you please pull up your shirt?
I'm here! Just hang on!
These things are really annoying.
Oh, here I can see now.
Glad that crisis is over.
I like it better this way.
You are not helping!
This is all too much!
I'm seriously going to cry!
Why does this have to
happen to little old me?
You got drunk and ran off!
This is 100 % your mess!
Well then why didn't you try and stop me?
I did, repeatedly!
You're right.
I was stupid and I'm sorry, now
please hurry up and save me!
That's what I've been trying
to do, but something's wrong!
I'm afraid I'm stuck like this!
The thing's above your head again. Oh, no.
Why is this happening now?
Is it possible that I'm unable to
move because deep in my subconscious,
I want to see Tachibana exposed like this?
No, stay focused.
That plant is already at the hair.
I can't afford to be distracted right now.
What can I do?
As long as I'm charmed, I'm useless.
Come on, think.
Last time, that slap cured the effect.
So it stands to reason another
severe shock could snap me out of it.
That's it!
Tachibana!
I need you to say something that
will shock me to my very core!
I'm not sure that's possible.
My life is so boring, I couldn't
even make my grandmother blush.
You have to try!
And please, do it quickly!
How about I take a nap instead?
Just do it already!
Peppers.
I refuse to eat them.
You're a 32-year-old man and you
still won't eat peppers? Really?
I'm not quite sure where this rage
came from, but it did the trick.
You doing all right over there?
Congratulations, you leveled up.
Screw you!
Listen here, buddy, you can deflect beams,
you're super strong
and you're still a guy!
But I got turned into a
defenseless little girl?
Who gets blind drunk off
one measly sip of beer!
and bell pepper suck!
I am not going to dignify
that with a response.
Why do all the worst of the
worst things happen to me?
I want to be reborn as a hot guy and
have loads of cute girls fun all over me!
My whole life I've been teased
for having a girly name!
Even my little sister
won't stop calling me Hina!
Tsukasa-Chinkuchi is a
super cutesy name too!
Why am I the only one getting picked on?
Oh, I see.
Now I understand why you gave the
heroine my name all those years ago.
Please don't cry, Tachibana?
It may sound selfish, but it
hurts me to see you this upset!
Come on, let's go home.
Hey, Jinguuji?
Hm?
Mother your spirit, between the two,
where do you think a person's gender lies?
Honestly, I think that whichever
you think is right, is right.
Is something the matter?
I swear this rule is
totally crap! I'm done!
You may look young, but you're
still a cranky old drunk.
Where did this come from?
This meat has a deliciously wild taste.
Let's go!
That's it! Yeah!
That's it! Happiness,
Yeah! Who are you
Yeah!
Who are you?
Days unquote finalist?
Love like that. Love Л어.
So honestанти.
You. go So.
you can go Come
on It's lonely Let's go Be almost That's.
good Ready?
Was it you okay?
Wait you Be okay, Littleле?
Like it!
Come!
Hey, Jinguji, the elf lady
is eating her guardian deity.
You think maybe we should step
in and tell her the truth?
Probably not.
Not knowing is to be as
Buddha, or so they say.
In her case, it's more
like her terrible goddess.